Oh, I'm sorry.
I had to do a vehicle dot vehicle.
Usually we just say from vehicle import the vehicle class.
But because I have to reload, we're kind of doing it this way.
Okay.
So now my 4 by 4, it has a make.
It has a model.
And it has a fuel.
I'm going to make a new instance of car.
So I'm going to say my Subaru is a vehicle dot cars.
And the make is Subaru.
And the model is cross track.
And the fuel is diesel.
I'm sorry I called it car.
So vehicle dot car.
Okay.
So I have my Subaru instance now.
My Subaru has a make.
My Subaru has a model.
My Subaru has fuel.
Does my Subaru have the number of wheels variable?
Does it?
It's always default.
That's right.
Does see what did I name it here?
My 4 by 4.
Does my 4 by 4 have a number of wheels?
Does it?
No.
Right?
Vehicle object has no attribute number of wheels.
My car does my vehicle doesn't.
And this is a good opportunity for me now.
If I wanted to make a motorcycle,
you can make a new class that has the default number of wheels to be two.
And that really kind of cuts down on data duplication.
Makes this code a lot more.
Composable a lot more easier to maintain.
Right?
If I had a method on vehicle.
Let's say, you know.
Is my fuel efficient?
Is eco friendly?
And I would take in self.
And if the fuel is equal to gas,
we're going to return false.
Otherwise, we're going to ever turn true.
My self.fuel, of course.
And I know that this self.fuel is always on my vehicle.
Even if I removed this, it wouldn't matter because the fuel here is by default gas.
So now I'm going to go in.
I'm going to reload this.
And then I'm going to say, you know,
I'm going to go back to my 4 by 4.
And make a new instance.
I'm going to make a new instance of my Subaru.
Subaru, cross track.
Does my 4 by 4?
Can I call this?
Is eco friendly?
Method on it?
Can I call it on my Subaru?
No, because you didn't bring it in in Subaru.
I didn't.
But what did I do here by calling a super dye net?
I made a called a net on my vehicle.
And my car inherits from vehicle.
So any methods available to my vehicle will also be available on my car.
That's how we encourage car code reuse.
If I made a new motorcycle class that inherited from vehicle,
it would also have this eco friendly method.
So instead of making motorcycle and car and a 4 by 4,
that all have their own version of this method,
we cut down on code duplication and put it in one place.
The last topic here, I'm not going to talk about very much.
I just want to give you a heads up.
Unlike in other languages, in Python, you can have multiple inheritance.
So you can inherit from multiple different other classes at once.
And things get a bit hairy, but one use case of this is something called a mixing.
So a mixing might be a class that just has a method like this on it.
And I don't care if my 4 by 4 is eco friendly.
I'm driving it through the grass and mowing it down.
And what do I care if it's, you know, gas or solar?
So where I, in the cases where I do care maybe like a car,
I can have an additional class that I inherit from that just has this method.
So one of my favorite, one common use case for this,
you might see if you're declaring database tables in Python.
You might have some mix-ins for something like a date column,
where you don't necessarily want, you want to have a date,
a created on date on all of your objects, just, you know, for compliance reasons.
But you don't want to have to say, you know, class vehicle dot date equals whatever,
class motor cycle dot date equals whatever.
So you can just have a mix-in class that will create that column for you.
And provide all of the methods that you might need to use it.
I've seen Python code that on an objects that don't,
or classes that don't inherit from anything else,
but the object keyword is the object that they inherit from,
instead of just saying the name of the class column,
they'll have object after the class definition.
So that is, yeah, that is one of the differences between Python 2 and Python 3.
In Python 3, you don't need to do that anymore.
It's redundant, you know,
simple as better than complex.
You can still do it, and it's not a syntax error.
You just shouldn't.